# **THOMAS ZEHE**

# **Full-stack Web Developer**

https://github.com/tzehe thzhdv@gmail.com www.thomaszehe.com 01778084875

### **PROFIL**

I am a passionate web developer who likes to build meaningful digital products. I believe in continuous learning, TDD, teamwork and agile project management. Developing well structured applications with a good user experience is a main focus of my work.

### **EXPERIENCE**

**IMMOBILIENSCOUT24** | Web Developer Geoservices Working Student April, 2017-Present | Berlin

Part of a team consisting of 4 engineers providing geo-related services. Geo-Autocompletion is the basis for location based searches on immobilienscout24.de. Shapeservice provides geo-json shapes for selected locations to enhance the search. GIS (Geographic Information System) used to geocode addresses.

Maintained all test pages and developed new features to the Shapeservice React.js test page which is a frontend to displays geo-json shapes on a Google map based on different search criterias.

Developed a new React.js based front-end for the Geo-autocompletion service to test the user experience for different clients.

Enhance Shapeservice to use OAuth2 with spring-security.

Analysed user data using a Zeppelin notebook an a Hadoop cluster based on Amazon EMR to improve the custom ranking of our Geo-autocompletion service.

Build helper tools applying principals of function programming to pre-process and filter geo data.

#### Related skills:

Javascript, React, react-router, recompose, Java, Python, Spring Boot, Elastic Search, AWS, Google Maps, Google Places, Intellij IDE

### FREELANCE | Web Developer

August, 2018-Present | Berlin

Developed a custom website for a client based on design specifications. Using React together with Next.js for server-side rendering to ensure faster page loads and better SEO. Implemented search components and add Google Services (Maps and Places).

#### Related skills:

Javascript, React, Next.js, Node.js, react-select, recompose, JSS, Google Maps, Google Places

https://github.com/tzehe thzhdv@gmail.com www.thomaszehe.com 01778084875

**IMMOBILIENSCOUT24** | System Administration Corporate IT Working Student September, 2016-March 2017

Part of the company IT-Support team helping employees with technical issues and did basic system administration tasks using Active Directory.

# **EDUCATION**

**TECHNISCHE UNIVERSITÄT BERLIN** | BSc. Business Informatics Oktober 2016 - Present

**TECHNISCHE UNIVERSITÄT BERLIN** | BSc. Media Computer Science Oktober 2014 - August 2016

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

General Languages: JavaScript (ES6), Java

Front-end Development: React.js, Next.js, CSS/JSS, Material-UI, Gatsby

Back-end Development: Node.js, Express, MongoDB, ElasticSearch, Docker, AWS

Tools: Git, Subversion, Jira, Intellij IDE, NPM